[Music]
hello everyone welcome back to my
channel I'm so happy you're here with me
the pink Cadillac talking all things
beauty and today I have probably one of
my favorite products ah
these three are a dynamite powerhouse of
summer protection like you guys need
these products I don't know what took me
so long
this company is already a year old but
one day I just took the leap of faith
and ordered all three of their products
and I've been hooked I've been using
these guys for about a month I wanted to
really give you a full picture and
really use them for a long time so I
could really tell you my full review of
everything and let me tell you these did
not disappoint they exceeded all of my
expectations and I'm super obsessed with
this brand the founder she is on
instagram at the 12-ish style which i
have a link below she's absolutely
amazing she is hilarious and I love
seeing her use these products in real
life it always makes me laugh and I was
just like you know what this is a
perfect time it's summer it's hot it's
sweaty you need these so without further
ado I should probably just tell you what
we're gonna talk about it is mega babe
yes yes mega babe
they have three products in lower-lying
and it comes in this cute adorable einie
package it came in the mail and i was
like so excited i was like oh my gosh
that's a pink package if you can see
there that's the front of it it has
these little stickers on it and it has
to make a big logo on it and I just love
the packaging I was just like I had to
keep it to show you because I was like
oh my gosh it's pink I'm obsessed
already so first one up is the daily
deodorant no aluminum no parabens the
Rosie pits so this is it right there
love their packaging love their logo
next one up is the bus dust
anti boob sweat spray and this is 100%
natural no talc and no
parabens so that's what that looks like
there and then the last one up is mega
babe sigh rescue anti chafe stick this
guy has aloe pomegranate grape seed oh
I'm gonna talk about like how much each
one cause the pros cons if there are any
so stay tuned if you want to see my full
review this brand mega babe was founded
by the 12-inch style which I call in
Instagram and I'm obsessed you have to
follow her
Katy's stir you know I think I'm saying
that right but Katy is hilarious and she
really you know founded these products
to help women who are are of all sizes I
think everyone deals with these issues
like I've never shaved so bad in my life
when I went to Paris and they were
having record temps and I decided like
shorts were a good idea and no skirt I
think I wore a skirt one day and it was
almost like 95 and I had the worst
chafing of my entire life I didn't even
know like that was a thing I was young I
think I was like 14 and it was these red
swollen bumps I literally had to sit in
the bathtub for like with ice-cold water
for like 20 minutes to like just ease
the pain of walking it's crazy you guys
chafing is so real and I like finally
resorted to these like spandex shorts
underneath but it's summer it's been a
105 degrees in Colorado and I don't know
what it is like why do we tell ourselves
like that is what we just have to do or
we have to chafe or you know our thighs
just rub together that's there's nothing
wrong with that it's fine and I don't
know why I'm like oh I have to wear
these shorts because my thighs are just
so big like the things you tell yourself
are just really weird you know and so
when I saw the first one out like let's
just go into it the thigh rescue the
anti chafe stick where has this been all
my life
literally I tried to use like a Monistat
product that I saw on some article and
it was okay
but I felt like I had to keep reapplying
it I went to a baseball game I wore a
dress and I was just like you know what
I'm I'm gonna go with it without my
spandex shorts for lunch which was so
freeing and incredible that feeling that
sense of just I'm just being me I'm
wearing what I want to wear I don't have
to worry about it
those black spandex shorts under
anything are so hot they're just
terrible and you're just sweaty down
there and it's gross I don't want that I
don't like that so when I put this on
it's so easy to apply and I love on her
Instagram she's just applying this in
day length she's just you know goes near
you know wherever she is and she just
like puts it on and like she's just
under her skirt and I'm just like yes
Carly yes this is what we need this is
what you you you can go anywhere I put
this on I was good the whole entire
night no chafing it smells wonderful it
goes on like so buttery smooth and it
stays like I was amazed and it's a toxic
free form that has vitamin E and aloe it
does keep you comfortable and cool just
like it says I wasn't really impressed
with this I kind of want like a travel
size so I can take this like in my purse
because this is a little big you do get
two point one two ounces my only
complaint but I did carry this in my
backpack that night at the baseball game
because it was like almost 100 degrees
and this worked like a frickin charm I
was so so blown away and so freeing like
I didn't even think about like wearing
the shorts and worrying about that and I
was just like it was just me it was just
me where he dressed like oh this is
amazing
I love those like I'm obsessed this guy
I did buy all three of their products
which was a total of 48 dollars and they
do get free shipping for that this runs
you $14 that's it you guys like what are
you waiting for this is incredible like
I cannot believe how hot it's been
lately here and I've just like been
reaching for this like non-step and it's
so great like I've put my shorts my bike
shorts away and I'm just like huh
because sometimes you're wearing a short
skirt you don't necessarily need those
like
they don't you'd have to hike them up
it's uncomfortable and girls we deserve
more than that our thighs red and that's
okay we've got a chaise stick for that
reason and that's all right I'm all for
this I can see this for running for
exercising for any sort of multi-purpose
activity it just smells so wonderful and
it's and it's delightful I had no issues
with I love this at you guys I love it
the taste stick thank you so much of her
just allowing us to be and it's huge I
think when you think about her line and
what it means for body positivity it's
incredible so next up my favorite
deodorant this is the daily deodorant in
the rosy pits it just comes caps off and
you've got the little thing here you
know it does take it's a natural
antibacterial blend for high-performing
invisible order protection coconut and
vitamin E also nourishes and I'm just
gonna tell you you guys I've been doing
the natural deodorant thing for a while
but it is a transition I am a sweaty
lady and it doesn't always start off
like a dream so this guy you are gonna
sweat at first and what I think really
helps with this I also cleanse my
underarms my armpits twice a day in the
morning I go in with a good Terkel type
of scrub or any sort of like that just
seems charcoal just seems to help with
the odor so that's why I go in there um
but I do rinse my pits out in the
morning and at night and it seems to be
helping quite a bit because of that
bacteria and things you just want to get
that out of there so it is a transition
if you're going into the natural side of
deodorant it is a little there is a bit
of adjustment period um so I did sweat
with this at first and she does
recommend to take the bus dust and
combine this so I'll put this on first
and then I'll spray a little bit of this
on with this so helpful and I do sweat
and I think that's something you just
have to get used to of just like it's
gonna it's hot it's just gonna be how it
is your body I think with all those
chemicals when you think about I used to
put on
at night like the really intense stuff
that made you like because it was bad I
would like have rings down to like my
bellybutton it was bad I'm just a sweaty
lady so this really keeps it at bay
I do sweat but it's not like as much
sweat as I was getting and I feel really
good knowing I'm not filling my body
with chemicals that's your lymph nodes
those are very sensitive areas and this
guy is completely natural
I love the rosy smell it's just it's not
overpowering it feels very ladylike I
think they are coming out that was my
only thing I want more sense of this guy
and I think they are coming out with
more so stay tuned for that because I do
think like having another like non
flowery scent would be really helpful
not everyone wants to smell like that in
some days I'm like yeah I don't feel
like I want to smell like a flower today
so that is amazing I'm really excited to
hear that they're doing that and so like
bus dust incredible I've seen this at
Ulta she is starting to sell her
products at Ulta and I just heard j.crew
but they sold out so quick and j.crew
Congrats girl you did it you're doing it
I'm so happy for you the best way to get
it is order it for through her website
but this is the bus dose anti boob sweat
spray oh you guys I didn't I just
thought I had to live with my boob sweat
and I thought that's just like what you
did oh it's really streams like these
things that you telling yourself like oh
this is just me I just have sweaty boobs
and like I'm a 34g like these girls are
not small by any means that's a lot of
like like lump you know that's a lot of
fat to carry around it does get hot
under there and it's kind of weird like
you know if you're going on a date you
don't want like your bra to be soaked
and you know it's just weird so I was so
freaking pumped for this I sprayed right
underneath I just lift and spray up
right underneath I love this little pump
applicator too because I think it just
missed out like the perfect like even
application of a little puff here I'll
do it for you isn't that beautiful
it's just a light light dusting of a
little spray there and it's just like
keeps the sweat at bay for me and it
works so well I even put it in my lady
bits you guys in my underwear it does
get kind of swampy down there so I
spritz a little bit this under my
armpits and under my my boobs and it's
amazing
like literally soaks everything up I am
like dry as a well I don't know dry is a
what I don't know I'm just like you take
off your prom and it's like there's no
sweat stains there's no weird odor like
it's incredible the feeling of like
you're just like huh I'm fresh I'm I'm
doing it I'm in this hot climate but I'm
feeling refreshed and I don't know how
she does it but this is a good
incredible combination for me I also has
bacteria fighting lavender and soothing
chamomile and it says shake well and
spray it under between and around
cleavage for a dry smooth finish so I am
really impressed
I can't you guys like literally this is
my go-to every single day a little bit
of this a little bit of this boobs
vagina hey bus test like is my like like
safer like I now I don't know what I
would do without these products they
have become such a staple in my routine
like I'm hooked what I love - she'd
never tests on animals and yeah it's
just like organic as well it hasn't been
irritating my skin at all it's you guys
the sign is incredible the best fit $48
I've ever spent the bus dust is 16 and
the Rosie Pitts is 18 you get quite a
bit of product in here - 2.6 ounces and
this is three ounces and you just shake
this guy up you're good to go again
great I do think the size is pretty good
to travel with it's just it's pretty
compact there are no complaints I even
feel like I could put this in my hair
and do like a little dry shampoo I
haven't tried it but um I feel like it's
an all-purpose like spray it's amazing
like you guys I love this line make it
babe I'm addicted I'm so obsessed I
think they just came out with another
product today some little wipes which
are I cannot wait to try that I may be
ordering that soon
so let me know if you want to hear about
how that was but Katie the whole mega
babe team you are crushing it and thank
you I didn't realize how much this just
helps my sanity and my being a curvy
girl is it's just so freeing to have
products that allow you to just be you
and to smell good and to feel good and
you're fresh and you're not chafing and
you can just be and you can live and you
don't have to make it like these weird
excuses in your head of how you have to
be that you just have to be a Chafee
sweaty lady because you don't you just I
just didn't have very products it's just
these were just missing in my life so oh
my gosh you need these in your life just
buy them i i cannot rave about these
enough yeah I'm so hooked on these so
thank you mega big team for just
allowing us to be and giving us products
that truly have changed my life I have
then it's just something I don't have to
think about I don't have to keep
reapplying I don't have to I'm just I
smell good I'm not shaved I'm not sweaty
it's amazing it's so good we all
everyone needs this I think everyone
chase everyone sweaty it's hot it's
summer so you need these get it give it
for your girlfriend buy one for you just
live just you know it's the best it is
the best purchase I've made and this
summer and these are pretty much
essentials in my cabinet now oh thank
you could be thank you think of aid I
can't say enough you can find it at Ulta
you can find it at J Crew online at mega
babe beauty.com and they are at mega
babe on instagram follow at the 12 estoy
you guys thank you so much for watching
for hearing all about my addiction for
letting me rave about it for so long you
guys are the best thank you so much and
I will see you back here for more videos
thank you so much for watching as always
fabulous
utterly you bye
you